Then it is a little dangerous.
There are 4 high pressure pumps that can handle 230 liters were flowing.
But if any gasoline management burst, it will be a disaster.
I was lucky when the tank burst.
The idea is below the spreaders.
Had it splashing up gasoline on glowing pipes it could have been a fireball.
The temperature increases about 100 degrees per second.
And when it starts, you have to get going right away.
The pulse dirt engine can be up to 10-15 seconds.
I have protective plates, but I can't sit as wide as possible.
The plate is so close to the pipes so the heat is not against so long.
When you stop gas, you have to move your feet from the footpegs.
Otherwise, the heat goes through the leather stand.